Do you know how many members of TLC there are?
Three.
How many members are there?
Because I'm going to keep it present tense.
Okay.
In the Migos.
Three.
Do you know how many members of Destiny's Child there are?
Well, it depends on what era.
So I'll take that as a yes.
Yes.
Okay.
How many senators are there?
In my state or?
In the United States.
How many senators sit in the Senate?
That's a lot of them.
Let's go with 600.
Well, 100.
Because there's two for each state.
Okay.
And there's 50 states.
I messed up.
It's all good.
This is what I'm saying.
A lot of us, we don't really know how this whole thing works.
You're right.
Which is why I feel like it needs to be more part of our culture,
the way that Destiny's Child and TLC are a part of our culture.
Yes, ma'am.
Tell me this.
Where was Donald Trump on January 6th?
Is this a trick question?
The answer to me, in the wrong place at the wrong time.
I say that's the right answer.